[{"answer": "I think what Barack Obama is going through (INAUDIBLE) than race.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since the inauguration of the first black president?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well, nobody has put a fine point on it but it's not hard to see why people might be outraged by Wall Street.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Do they know what they're protesting about?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes, but I'm not sure what the bankruptcy of Harrisburg means.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Now when whole towns in America starts declaring themselves bankrupt, this is a sign that this is pretty serious, isn't it?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Well, America has been living beyond its means for a generation.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "But is America basically bust financially?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "So you've got to accept that -- like everyone else in the world when I answer that question, I'm just guessing.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "And where do you see this politically?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "There were a couple of reasons.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Why did you go looking for whatever it was you found?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you probably give monks too much credit just to start with.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "I mean when you have monks who are behaving like this, hasn't the whole world basically lost its entire moral compass?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, I hope you come back on and talk to me about it when it's done.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "So I'll tell you after I'm done, how about that?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Thanks for having me.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Is that a deal?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "The first time I met Martin Luther King in the basement of a church in Harlem.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "If I had that power, what would it be?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Humble, without false modesty, eloquent, intellectual, extremely intellectual and highly intelligent.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "There's no question we have realized a good portion of it.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "How far do you think America has come in realizing Martin Luther King's dream?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "No, I do not.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Do you see that anymore in modern leaders?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I had hoped very much that he would be that person.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "How did you feel when he got elected?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Certainly the amount of social activism, we are less racist than appearance.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since the inauguration of the first black president?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I subscribed to it.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What did you think when he said that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I felt that something very important had been revealed.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What did you feel when that happened?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I'm glad I sung it.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Or do you wish you had never sung the damn thing?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "\"Try to Remember,\" a great ballad from the Fantastics.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What are your personal other favorite songs?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Like many, I was certainly in awe of his great gift and his talent.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What was your view of him?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I think, along the way, there are individuals that intervene that help you to see a brighter side to things and can help -- you can trust their view of what they say about you and the distortions you may be living through.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Or in the end, do you yourself have to do with these things?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "There are two things that have defined me.", "docId": "111013pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "When you look back, how would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 521}]